{
  "0": [
    {
      "id": "r01_1",
      "question": "01",
      "response": "1",
      "left": "1.5%",
      "top": "78.17%",
      "width": "66.5%",
      "height": "20.67%",
      "polygon": "0.25% 19.35%, 29.07% 17.74%, 47.12% 12.9%, 66.92% 0.0%, 79.95% 0.0%, 85.46% 5.65%, 100.0% 61.29%, 84.21% 93.55%, 17.29% 96.77%, 3.26% 92.74%"
    },
    {
      "id": "r01_2",
      "question": "01",
      "response": "2",
      "left": "52.5%",
      "top": "64.83%",
      "width": "46.5%",
      "height": "32.0%",
      "polygon": "8.96% 0.52%, 99.64% 35.42%, 99.64% 99.48%, 27.24% 67.71%, 1.43% 29.69%, 0.72% 16.67%"
    },
    {
      "id": "r01_3",
      "question": "01",
      "response": "3",
      "left": "0.83%",
      "top": "56.33%",
      "width": "52.17%",
      "height": "26.17%",
      "polygon": "0.64% 2.55%, 44.09% 16.56%, 96.49% 44.59%, 98.72% 57.96%, 99.36% 72.61%, 93.61% 78.98%, 86.58% 84.71%, 75.4% 89.81%, 63.26% 93.63%, 49.84% 96.18%, 33.23% 98.09%, 1.6% 97.45%"
    },
    {
      "id": "r01_4",
      "question": "01",
      "response": "4",
      "left": "55.83%",
      "top": "39.83%",
      "width": "43.17%",
      "height": "28.83%",
      "polygon": "8.49% 6.36%, 17.37% 0.58%, 51.74% 7.51%, 66.41% 10.98%, 99.23% 6.94%, 99.23% 96.53%, 20.46% 94.22%, 1.16% 80.92%, 0.77% 34.68%"
    },
    {
      "id": "r01_5",
      "question": "01",
      "response": "5",
      "left": "0.17%",
      "top": "31.67%",
      "width": "55.83%",
      "height": "34.67%",
      "polygon": "3.88% 0.96%, 81.19% 27.88%, 100.0% 49.52%, 100.0% 85.1%, 91.94% 99.52%, 76.72% 95.67%, 42.69% 81.25%, 1.79% 51.92%"
    }
  ],
  "1": [
    {
      "id": "r02_1",
      "question": "02",
      "response": "1",
      "left": "30.83%",
      "top": "24.0%",
      "width": "42.17%",
      "height": "10.33%",
      "polygon": "0.4% 1.61%, 99.6% 1.61%, 99.6% 51.61%, 75.49% 56.45%, 64.82% 67.74%, 55.34% 83.87%, 51.78% 88.71%, 44.66% 87.1%, 28.46% 62.9%, 19.37% 51.61%, 7.91% 41.94%, 5.14% 40.32%, 0.4% 40.32%"
    },
    {
      "id": "r02_2",
      "question": "02",
      "response": "2",
      "left": "26.5%",
      "top": "29.83%",
      "width": "49.5%",
      "height": "14.0%",
      "polygon": "0.34% 1.19%, 28.96% 2.38%, 49.49% 34.52%, 61.28% 14.29%, 78.11% 2.38%, 88.55% -1.19%, 99.66% 0.0%, 100.0% 78.57%, 84.51% 57.14%, 72.39% 59.52%, 64.98% 70.24%, 56.9% 83.33%, 52.86% 92.86%, 47.47% 94.05%, 44.11% 90.48%, 39.06% 80.95%, 18.52% 51.19%, 10.77% 51.19%, 0.34% 53.57%"
    },
    {
      "id": "r02_3",
      "question": "02",
      "response": "3",
      "left": "17.33%",
      "top": "36.5%",
      "width": "65.0%",
      "height": "20.33%",
      "polygon": "23.85% 2.46%, 33.08% 9.02%, 51.28% 37.7%, 53.08% 37.7%, 56.92% 28.69%, 63.85% 15.57%, 70.26% 10.66%, 75.64% 9.02%, 83.85% 11.48%, 91.28% 22.95%, 96.92% 45.9%, 99.23% 61.48%, 100.26% 81.15%, 98.72% 100.0%, 84.62% 100.0%, 81.28% 71.31%, 75.9% 65.57%, 69.74% 63.93%, 64.87% 68.03%, 60.51% 75.41%, 56.67% 85.25%, 54.1% 92.62%, 52.31% 97.54%, 48.46% 97.54%, 45.38% 86.07%, 42.05% 76.23%, 33.33% 59.84%, 27.18% 57.38%, 22.31% 59.02%, 17.18% 69.67%, 14.62% 81.15%, 13.85% 99.18%, 0.77% 99.18%, 0.51% 63.93%, 4.62% 36.07%, 10.51% 17.21%, 15.64% 7.38%"
    },
    {
      "id": "r02_4",
      "question": "02",
      "response": "4",
      "left": "26.5%",
      "top": "48.67%",
      "width": "46.5%",
      "height": "19.5%",
      "polygon": "18.28% 2.56%, 29.75% 5.13%, 40.5% 20.51%, 50.54% 45.3%, 58.42% 29.06%, 70.61% 9.4%, 78.85% 5.13%, 87.46% 7.69%, 91.4% 11.11%, 94.98% 23.93%, 97.85% 40.17%, 98.92% 65.81%, 94.62% 99.15%, 86.74% 100.85%, 84.59% 86.32%, 78.85% 74.36%, 75.27% 70.94%, 64.87% 74.36%, 56.63% 86.32%, 51.97% 95.73%, 50.18% 96.58%, 43.01% 81.2%, 32.62% 70.94%, 23.66% 70.94%, 20.07% 81.2%, 19.0% 98.29%, 7.53% 99.15%, 0.72% 64.96%, 0.36% 25.64%, 4.3% 10.26%, 9.68% 2.56%"
    },
    {
      "id": "r02_5",
      "question": "02",
      "response": "5",
      "left": "34.83%",
      "top": "61.83%",
      "width": "32.5%",
      "height": "20.83%",
      "polygon": "8.72% 3.2%, 18.46% 3.2%, 30.77% 10.4%, 41.54% 21.6%, 46.15% 30.4%, 56.41% 20.0%, 66.67% 8.0%, 80.51% 4.0%, 86.15% 6.4%, 92.31% 15.2%, 97.44% 29.6%, 97.44% 37.6%, 100.0% 99.2%, 0.51% 99.2%, 2.05% 19.2%"
    }
  ],
  "2": [
    {
      "id": "r03_1",
      "question": "03",
      "response": "1",
      "left": "29.5%",
      "top": "85.5%",
      "width": "38.0%",
      "height": "12.33%",
      "polygon": "8.33% 1.35%, 93.86% 1.35%, 99.56% 14.86%, 99.12% 100.0%, 0.44% 102.7%, 0.44% 27.03%"
    },
    {
      "id": "r03_2",
      "question": "03",
      "response": "2",
      "left": "33.5%",
      "top": "73.17%",
      "width": "29.33%",
      "height": "12.0%",
      "polygon": "20.45% 2.78%, 87.5% 2.78%, 100.0% 105.56%, 1.14% 102.78%"
    },
    {
      "id": "r03_3",
      "question": "03",
      "response": "3",
      "left": "40.5%",
      "top": "60.67%",
      "width": "17.83%",
      "height": "12.0%",
      "polygon": "0.93% 2.78%, 100.93% 4.17%, 98.13% 98.61%, -0.93% 93.06%"
    },
    {
      "id": "r03_4",
      "question": "03",
      "response": "4",
      "left": "23.5%",
      "top": "45.67%",
      "width": "47.0%",
      "height": "14.83%",
      "polygon": "0.35% 2.25%, 100.35% 3.37%, 82.27% 101.12%, 33.69% 98.88%, 9.57% 51.69%"
    },
    {
      "id": "r03_5",
      "question": "03",
      "response": "5",
      "left": "20.33%",
      "top": "30.33%",
      "width": "56.67%",
      "height": "14.83%",
      "polygon": "1.76% 3.37%, 99.41% 4.49%, 91.47% 98.88%, 4.71% 98.88%, 0.0% 62.92%"
    }
  ],
  "3": [
    {
      "id": "r04_1",
      "question": "04",
      "response": "1",
      "left": "5.0%",
      "top": "77.5%",
      "width": "88.33%",
      "height": "21.67%",
      "polygon": "9.06% 2.31%, 13.21% 23.85%, 17.36% 36.92%, 23.21% 49.23%, 29.43% 58.46%, 37.55% 66.92%, 48.49% 72.31%, 60.19% 73.08%, 66.6% 70.0%, 72.83% 66.92%, 79.62% 57.69%, 83.4% 47.69%, 86.04% 37.69%, 88.3% 26.92%, 91.13% 13.08%, 92.83% 2.31%, 99.81% 1.54%, 99.81% 97.69%, 0.75% 97.69%, 0.57% 2.31%"
    },
    {
      "id": "r04_2",
      "question": "04",
      "response": "2",
      "left": "11.33%",
      "top": "71.5%",
      "width": "77.83%",
      "height": "21.0%",
      "polygon": "8.99% 0.79%, 14.13% 29.37%, 18.42% 42.86%, 23.34% 53.97%, 31.26% 67.46%, 37.04% 74.6%, 42.61% 76.98%, 49.68% 80.16%, 58.03% 77.78%, 65.52% 72.22%, 73.02% 62.7%, 79.87% 50.0%, 86.3% 30.95%, 90.79% 11.9%, 92.51% 1.59%, 99.79% 2.38%, 98.07% 19.84%, 94.22% 41.27%, 88.65% 65.87%, 81.8% 84.13%, 76.87% 92.86%, 73.23% 96.83%, 67.88% 98.41%, 60.81% 100.79%, 54.18% 101.59%, 48.39% 101.59%, 42.18% 100.0%, 38.97% 97.62%, 34.9% 96.83%, 31.26% 94.44%, 25.48% 87.3%, 20.34% 80.95%, 14.13% 71.43%, 8.99% 58.73%, 4.93% 42.06%, 1.5% 24.6%, 0.64% 14.29%, 0.43% 2.38%"
    },
    {
      "id": "r04_3",
      "question": "04",
      "response": "3",
      "left": "17.0%",
      "top": "64.17%",
      "width": "67.67%",
      "height": "23.67%",
      "polygon": "5.67% 1.41%, 6.4% 12.68%, 8.13% 24.65%, 11.08% 33.8%, 14.53% 40.85%, 19.21% 52.11%, 24.88% 60.56%, 32.02% 66.2%, 39.41% 71.13%, 47.04% 73.94%, 51.97% 73.94%, 59.11% 71.13%, 65.76% 66.9%, 71.92% 61.97%, 78.08% 55.63%, 80.79% 53.52%, 83.99% 47.18%, 86.95% 37.32%, 89.41% 28.17%, 91.13% 16.2%, 92.36% 8.45%, 92.61% 2.11%, 99.26% 2.11%, 99.51% 10.56%, 99.01% 21.83%, 98.03% 29.58%, 95.81% 41.55%, 92.36% 53.52%, 89.66% 59.86%, 85.71% 69.01%, 81.77% 76.76%, 75.62% 85.21%, 70.44% 90.85%, 63.3% 95.77%, 55.17% 98.59%, 49.75% 100.0%, 46.31% 100.0%, 42.36% 99.3%, 37.93% 97.89%, 33.74% 95.77%, 28.33% 91.55%, 22.17% 84.51%, 17.0% 76.76%, 11.82% 65.49%, 7.64% 54.23%, 3.94% 41.55%, 1.48% 28.87%, 0.25% 16.2%, 0.49% 7.04%, 0.49% 2.11%"
    },
    {
      "id": "r04_4",
      "question": "04",
      "response": "4",
      "left": "21.83%",
      "top": "63.67%",
      "width": "57.17%",
      "height": "18.17%",
      "polygon": "10.2% 2.75%, 11.08% 13.76%, 12.24% 22.02%, 14.87% 30.28%, 18.37% 37.61%, 20.99% 42.2%, 24.78% 47.71%, 35.57% 58.72%, 43.44% 63.3%, 48.4% 66.06%, 53.06% 66.06%, 58.89% 64.22%, 64.72% 62.39%, 72.01% 56.88%, 78.72% 47.71%, 85.42% 34.86%, 87.17% 23.85%, 87.76% 1.83%, 99.71% 1.83%, 99.71% 23.85%, 97.67% 36.7%, 95.92% 44.04%, 93.88% 52.29%, 92.13% 58.72%, 89.8% 66.06%, 88.05% 69.72%, 76.97% 81.65%, 70.85% 87.16%, 64.43% 91.74%, 59.18% 94.5%, 55.1% 97.25%, 51.6% 97.25%, 48.98% 97.25%, 45.19% 97.25%, 41.4% 95.41%, 36.15% 92.66%, 29.74% 88.99%, 23.03% 82.57%, 18.08% 76.15%, 15.16% 71.56%, 11.08% 62.39%, 7.29% 52.29%, 3.21% 40.37%, 1.46% 33.03%, 0.87% 25.69%, 0.58% 2.75%"
    },
    {
      "id": "r04_5",
      "question": "04",
      "response": "5",
      "left": "28.67%",
      "top": "55.5%",
      "width": "43.33%",
      "height": "19.5%",
      "polygon": "2.69% 17.95%, 18.08% 4.27%, 79.23% 3.42%, 96.15% 27.35%, 98.85% 41.03%, 99.23% 61.54%, 96.92% 70.94%, 93.08% 79.49%, 87.31% 86.32%, 83.46% 89.74%, 78.08% 94.02%, 72.69% 97.44%, 68.85% 99.15%, 64.62% 99.15%, 32.31% 97.44%, 24.23% 93.16%, 19.62% 88.03%, 13.08% 82.05%, 8.08% 76.92%, 3.85% 68.38%, 1.92% 63.25%, 1.15% 58.12%, 1.15% 23.08%"
    }
  ]
}